{
    "subject": "Connie_Booth",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "John_Cleese",
    "human_readable": "Connie Booth is married to John Cleese.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9337877035140991,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Connie Booth and John Cleese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9223073720932007,
            "question": "Who is Connie Booth married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131260514259338,
            "question": "Is John Cleese married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8709023594856262,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Connie Booth and John Cleese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8697669506072998,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Connie Booth."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8265495896339417,
            "question": "Who is the husband of Connie Booth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6902139782905579,
            "question": "To whom is Connie Booth connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6442115306854248,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Connie Booth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6299206614494324,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marital status of John Cleese?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1933594048023224,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Connie Booth is married to John Cleese.",
            "html": "yago_28798_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marital status of John Cleese?",
            "html": "yago_28798_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Connie Booth?",
            "html": "yago_28798_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Connie Booth connected?",
            "html": "yago_28798_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28798_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Connie Booth is married to John Cleese. The documents mention that they were married for ten years (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28798/re-ranker-msmarco/63.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28798/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt) and that they co-wrote the sitcom \"Fawlty Towers\" together (from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28798/re-ranker-msmarco/63.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Connie Booth was married to John Cleese, including details about their marriage and divorce. Therefore, the statement \"Connie Booth is married to John Cleese\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}